SAMUEL G. MUNOZ

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

Career Objective

Doing undergraduate research on the Collatz Conjecture in college made me realize that a career in academia was not a good fit for me. For the next 2 years I diligently saved money from being an Amazon Delivery Associate, in order to take the Full-Stack Web Development certificate offered by Noble Desktop. I am a young, aspiring and hard-working immigrant looking to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company.

Contact

✓ samuel1698500@gmail.com

**** (917) 769-9619

• Copiague, NY, 11726

Education

QUEENSBOROUGH COMMUNITY COLLEGE GPA: 3.8

Queens, NY Associate in Liberal Arts in Science & Math (May 2019)

Extracurricular Activities
Undergraduate Research in Math

Additional Skills

Ruby on Rails Javascript/jQuery CSS Flex/Grid APIs

Certifications

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate by Noble Desktop

Experience

Apr 2021 - Present

RUBY ON RAILS WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance, Copiague, NY

- Design, build, or maintain web sites, using authoring or scripting languages, content creation tools, management tools, and digital media.
- Evaluate code to ensure that it is valid, is properly structured, meets industry standards and is compatible with browsers, devices, or operating systems.
- Create searchable indices for web page content.
- Currently working on https://github.com/Samuel1698/PinkWug.live

Sep 2019 - Apr 2021

AMAZON DELIVERY ASSOCIATE

DTO Logistics, Bethpage, NY

- Inspect and maintain vehicle supplies and equipment, such as gas, oil, water, tires, lights, or brakes, to ensure that vehicles are in proper working condition.
- Report any mechanical problems encountered with vehicles.

Sep 2017 - May 2019

• Load and unload trucks, vans, or automobiles.

SUPPLEMENTAL INSTRUCTOR

Queensborough Community College, Queens, NY

- Prepare course materials such as syllabi, class assignments, and handouts.
- Initiate, facilitate, and moderate classroom discussions.
- Maintain regularly scheduled office hours to advise and assist students.
- Plan, evaluate, and revise curricula, course content, and course materials and methods of instruction.
- Collaborate with colleagues to address teaching and research issues.